我不会让你们这些穴居人掠夺我的公司
I'm not letting you Neanderthals in to rape my company.
翻译　水平有限的皮带断了
字　　幕　　侠
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
我的提案太他妈好了 你不得不接受
This is a deal so fucking good, you have to take it,
后期　Jason肖　特效　小布
ZIMUXIA.CN
校对　水平有限的皮带断了　时间轴　阿布
否则我们法庭见
or we'll see you in court.
原 创 翻 译
中英双语字幕
压制　Jason肖
我们需要讨论这次熊抱策略 坚持还是卖掉
We need to discuss this bear hug: stick or sell?
监制　水平有限的皮带断了
ZIMUXIA.CN
原 创 翻 译
中英双语字幕
我想你应该打一仗
I think you should fight.
-这一切都是你建造的  -哇 真动听
- You're the one who built it all. - Oh, that was adorable.
你总是在找爸爸 不是吗
You're always looking out for Pops, aren't you?
我想正式请你进入公司
I'd like to formally ask you to come in
担当下一任首席执行官
to be the next chief executive of this company.
你是唯一合适的人选
You're the one.
目前 我们需要保守这个秘密
For now we need to keep this between us,
-我要想想汤姆 吉尔  -当然
- everything about Tom, Gil. - Of course.
他说什么 我要去管哪里
What did he say? Where am I going?
你这是要给我什么他妈的好消息啊 有多好啊
What have you fucking landed me? Is it huge?
全球广播新闻的要职
Chair of global broadcast news.
泛美网络科技 宝贝
ATN, baby.
肯德尔和罗曼将担任联合首席运营官
Kendall and Roman will act as co-chief operating officers.
你刚刚是说联合吗
Did you just say co-chief?
不 他又回公司了吗
No, he's coming back?
看看风把谁吹来了
Look what the cat dragged in.
他想让我告诉你们 你们会损失大量金钱
He wanted me to tell you you're going to bleed cash,
他也会损失大量金钱
he's going to bleed cash,
也许你们能干掉他 但是如果你们没有干掉他 他就会干掉你们
and maybe you'll kill him, but if you don't, he aims to kill you.
我们将成为世界上
We're going to be the number one
最大的传媒集团
media conglomerate in the world.
说得真好
Hear, hear.
我们可以进去吗 这是怎么回事
Can we get in? What's going on?
我们走吧
Let's go.
我们看看他是不是还醒着
Let's see if he's still awake.
那是他吗
Is that him?
好的 我们可以大喊
Okay. Can we yell,
"醒醒 雪乔"
"Wake up, Snow Joe!"
醒醒 雪乔
Wake up, Snow Joe!
他在那儿
There he is.
你杵在这干啥 蠢猪
What's poppin', cum-dump?
嗯 只是在享受我女儿的生日 所以...
Yeah, just enjoying my daughter's birthday, so...
爸爸 我们所有项目都玩过了
Daddy, uh, we've tried everything.
他们可以让货车列车更快吗
Can they make the wagon train go faster?
我们... 问问吧
Let's... Let's ask, yeah?
货车列车可以再快点吗
Can the wagon train go any faster?
呃 可以快一点
Uh, up to a point.
很好 那就快那么一点 谢谢
Yeah, great. Let's take it up to that point. Thanks.
谢谢爸爸
Thanks, Daddy.
标牌太狗屎了
The signage is for shit.
你知道 现在还有其他一些傻逼问题
You know, still, some other sucker's problem now.
三个月前 我正在开会讨论如何阻止孩子
Three months ago, I was at a meeting about how to stop kids
在失控的幽灵列车上给对方打飞机
giving each other handy jobs on the runaway ghost train.
而现在 我即将开始管理
And now, I'm about to start managing
十亿美元的新闻预算了 所以... 一切都很好
a billion-dollar news budget, so... It's all good.
我第一次给人打飞机就是在幽灵列车上
I gave my first hand job on the ghost train.
我现在有一个讨厌的室友 所以我...
I have a shitty roommate right now, so I'm...
打算从这开始继续前进
trying to move on from that.
我朋友的公寓有间空房
My friend has an open room in her apartment.
-真的吗  -是的
- Oh, really? - Yeah, I mean,
但是 她有霉菌孢子的问题
she has an issue with spores from mold,
我不知道 我不知道你的肺对孢子有没有反应
but I don't know. I don't know how your lungs are with spores.
我确实看过一套房子
You know, I did see one place,
56平米
uh, 600 square feet.
但是 在史坦顿岛
But it was out in Staten Island.
-什么  -我不知道...
- What? - I dunno if...
格雷格表侄要搬去史坦顿岛吗
Cousin Greg is moving to Staten Island?
不 不 我不知道
No, no. I dunno.
天啊 你们听到了吗
Oh my God, did you hear this?
我只是在看那里的一个地方
I'm just looking at a place out there.
格雷格要乘渡轮上下班吗
Greg is getting the ferry to work?
看看布莱恩·费瑞
Check out Bryan Ferry.
伙计 为什么说到渡轮就不聊了
Dude, why stop at the ferry?
你才从克利夫兰坐灰狗巴士过来的
Just come in from Cleveland on the Greyhound.
你考虑过住酒店吗
Have you considered a hotel?
是过夜还是...
As, like, nightly, or... ?
洛根要求您去4号会议室
Logan's requested your presence in meeting room 4.
-哪个  -你们俩
- Which? - Both of you.
那就好玩了
Oh. That'll be fun.
瘪四和瘾君子
Beavis and Crackhead.
嗯 洛根也要求你加入
Um, Logan also asked for you to join, too.
-真的吗  -是的
- Oh, really? - Yeah.
好的
Oh. Okay.
-你要这个吗  -不要
- You wanna take this? - No.
他们都走了 走向老爸
Off they all go again, marching off to Daddy.
就像俄罗斯人加入布鲁西洛夫攻势一样
Like Russians joining the Brusilov Offensive.
第一次世界大战
World War I.
哦 是的 是的 是的 对
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Right.
我的重点是让韦斯达·罗伊科集团
My focus is bringing Waystar Royco
充分发挥其潜力
to its full earning potential.
那么 韦斯达拒绝收购
So, uh, Waystar refused to play ball?
我估计他们在你面前挥舞着毒丸
I'm assuming they waved a poison pill in your face
[公司为避免被对方兼并而向对方索取极高代价的阻挠措施]
现在你要发动一场代理权争夺战
and now you're launching a proxy battle
给董事会换血
to replace the board.
这家伙 他妈的假阳具蘸着胡须装饰
This guy, fuckin' dildo dipped in beard trimmings.
他在电视上屌我们
He's fuckin' us on TV.
当然 是皮尔斯让他上场的
And of course Pierce put him on.
是的 我们正在发动一场代理权争夺战
Yes, we're launching into a proxy battle...
他妈的自以为是的蠢猪
Self-righteous fuckin' butter-wouldn't-melt,
毫无诚信的普利策奖傻屌
disingenuous Pulitzer pricks.
洛根·罗伊是否适合
Is Logan Roy fit
运营一个21世纪的媒体组织
to run a 21st-century media organization?
你记得这些话吗 儿子
You recognize any of this, son?
这是剧本里写好的 爸爸
It's from the playbook, Dad.
哦 是的 当然是剧本
Oh, yes, of course, the playbook.
当然
Sure.
让我说清楚
Let me just make it very clear.
肯德尔·罗伊跟收购毫无瓜葛了
Kendall Roy is no longer relevant.
现在 关于桑迪·弗尼斯...
Now, with regards to Sandy Furness...
那...
So...
我们不表态 对他们不屑一顾
We keep our counsel. Dismissive.
把这些全部放在我们的股东委托书里面
Just lay it all out in our proxy statement.
匆忙的公众反应会让我们看起来很慌乱
A hurried public response makes us look rattled.
就这样让斯图威先去左右所有股东
So let Stewy sway all the shareholders first
我爸就这样傻傻坐着挨干吗
while Dad sits there with his thumb up his ass?
妙计啊
That's a great plan.
-嘿 小西  -我们先喘息一下
- Hey, Shiv. - Respectfully, we just take a beat.
我先准备好牢固的防御
Let me, uh, put a solid pack together.
等我们有弹药时 就还击
We fire back when we have the ammo.
到那时候枪战都结束了
By which point all the shooting's over.
不 现在就放出一份加料的版本
No, get out now with a salty re-frame.
这是低级下贱的企业掠夺者
This is your standard-issue basic-bitch corporate raider
和传奇的自然之力抗衡的标准回应方式
versus a fuckin' legendary force of nature,
飓风洛根
Hurricane Logan.
他有过一次快球 但...
He had a fastball once, but...
现在 今天
Now. Today.
卡罗丽娜来斟酌小西说的这些
Karolina runs the words past Shiv.
对 沃尔特公司
Yeah, Vaulter.
-嗯 好的  -沃尔特 他付了太多了去收购...
- Yeah. Okay. - Vaulter. He paid too big...
-对  -非常失望...
- Right. - Huge disappoi...
非常令人失望
It's a huge disappointment.
你觉得他们在骗我们吗
Do you think they suckered us?
-谁 沃尔特吗  -嗯
- Who, Vaulter? - Uh-huh.
不 我们深入研究过 我们... 我们...
No, we went deep on that. We... We...
事先的核查做得很好
kicked the tires good.
我觉得我们被骗了
I think we got chiseled.
收入预测越来越低
Revenue projections down and down.
我想我们搞砸了
I think we got screwed.
我也这么认为 砸得稀巴烂了 肯 烂大了
Yeah, me too. Massive fuck-up, Ken. Huge.
不可饶恕
Unforgivable.
对 我希望今天就把我们的回应发出去
Right, I want the response out today.
沃尔特也要解决好
I need Vaulter fixed.
行吗
All right?
这样我在投资者会议上才他妈的有话说
So I have something to say in my fucking investor meetings.
-快去  -好 我吗
- Go. - Okay. Me?
你们俩都去 谁解决了...
Both of you. One who fixes it...
奖个饼干
gets a cookie.
包在我身上 爸爸
You got it. Sure thing, Dad.
我... 我只想说谢谢你 嗯...
I... I just wanted to say thank you for, um...
为我们关闭公园的营业
closing down the park for us.
苏菲...
Sophie...
她过了一个很愉快的生日 她见到了雪乔...
she's having a great birthday. She got to meet Snow Joe and...
所以 谢谢你
So thank you.
看看你 破碎的机器人
Look at you, broken robot.
甚至连自己的孩子都不能拥抱
Can't even hug your own kids.
对 我看到了 怪胎
Yeah, I saw that, you freak.
小可爱
Pinkie.
开心吗
Happy?
是啊 厉害
Yeah. Smart.
你需要什么就告诉我
Uh, let me know if you need anything.
继     承
第 二 季  第２集
再见 玛丽莲
Bye, Marilyn.
再见 蒙代尔
Bye, Mondale.
你知道吗 我不在乎
You know what? I don't care.
这面空墙
This empty wall.
这里 我不在乎它是否丑得令人难以置信
Here. I don't care if it's incredibly gauche,
但是 这上面我们能不能不要只挂一幅
but can we not just have a big, beautiful portrait of us
漂亮的大肖像
up there?
-小西  -嗯
- Shiv. - Mm?
-太萨达姆了吗  -嗯
- Too Saddam? - Mm.
萨达姆喜欢挂个人肖像画]
-太阿萨德了吗[同上]  -嗯
- Too Assady? - Mm.
好吧
Okay.
-你好吗  -我好吗 我很好
- You good? - Am I good? I am great!
我很好 我很好 我睡得很好 呃...
I am great. I'm good. I slept well and, uh...
嗯 你知道我们的那件事吗 呃...
Yeah, you know your thing about us? Uh...
我想我已经在实际考虑了...
I think I've contextualized it...
-现在还是虚幻的  -不 不 不 当然
- It's not really a thing. - No, no, no, sure.
我只是觉得 "好的 你知道吗
I just feel like, "Okay, you know,
如果我是国王而你是女王
if I'm the king and you're the queen,
也许 干死那个...
maybe it's fine to...
奇怪的农民也不错"
fuck the odd peasant."
-对 是啊  -因为... 因为...
- Right. Yeah. - Because... Because...
大局来看 我们的计划步入正轨了
Big picture: our plan is right on track.
-你懂吗  -嗯
- You know? - Uh-huh.
而且你... 你见过吉尔的民调数据了 对吗
And you've... you've seen Gil's numbers, right?
而且... 截至今天 我正好在泛美网络科技就职
And... And as of today, I'm right in at ATN.
你知道 野兽的肚子里[核心层]
You know, belly of the beast.
所以...
So...
-嘿  -怎么了
- Hey. - Yeah?
想来一发吗 就现在
You wanna bang? Right now?
厚脸皮的早餐炮
Cheeky little breakfast bang.
-哦... 我...  -想吗
- Oh... I'm... - Wanna?
我现在没这层心思...
I'm just such in a different mental place...
-好的  -...不像你
- Okay. - ... than you right now.
没事 没关系
No, sure.
我只是觉得自己非常强大
I just feel so incredibly potent.
-嗯  -你懂吗
- Mm. - You know?
我觉得是因为这套新房子
I think it's the new place.
-是的  -你知道吗
- Yeah. - You know?
-我感觉像神一样 充满了欲望  -哦
- I feel God-like and horny. - Oof!
对我来说 每个人看起来都像小矮人
Everybody looks, like, two feet tall to me.
嗯 你知道吗 也许...
Well, you know what? Maybe...
也许我们今晚应该早点摆脱公事
Maybe we should split from the thing early
你懂的 我们可以...
tonight and, you know, we can...
-聊聊 然后...  -嗯嗯
- talk, and... - Mm-hmm.
-...想"干"嘛干嘛  -好的
- ... everything. - Okay!
好的 我最喜欢这样了 谈战略加打炮
Okay! My fave. Strategy and a fuck.
-好的 再见  -祝你今天顺利
- Okay, bye. - Have a good one.
再见 宝贝
Bye, honey.
非常酷 你知道吗 他们楼上有自己的蜂箱
So cool. You know they have their own beehive upstairs?
干什么用 那是他妈的商业模式吗
What is that? Is that, like, the fucking business model?
冲突色情和潮人宝贝
Conflict porn and hipster honey.
切
Oh, shh.
假记者们在假装工作呢
The pretend journalists are pretend working.
好了 罗曼 冷静吧
All right, Rome, just cool it.
好好走 慢慢走 行吗
Let's move nice and slow here. Yeah?
-嗯嗯  -步子小一点 正常点
- Mm-hmm. - Just keep it small and general.
我们可不想吓到他
We don't wanna spook him.
好的 听你的 你说了算
Yeah, okay. You got it. You are in charge.
我跟着你的领导 混蛋
I follow your lead, fucker.
劳瑞·易 纽约之王
Larry Yee, King of New York!
搞什么呢
What the fuck?
感谢你抽空 我知道事出紧急
Thanks for making space, man. I know it was last minute.
老兄 随时欢迎
Ah, dude. Anytime.
嘿 劳伦斯
Hey, Lawrence.
我听说你被禁锢在城堡里了
I heard you were drying out in a Schloss,
和家庭妇女们一起做恶心的瑜伽呢
doing shitty yoga with hausfrau?
对 对
Right. right.
不
Nope.
他回来了 他卷土重来了 就像是得到了假释
He is back. He is back, like a pedo on parole.
是的 伙计 我们只是来聊聊
Yeah, man, we're just here for a catch-up.
你懂的 超级随意 脚可以放在桌子上 想怎么随便就怎么来
You know? Super casual, feet on the table, whatever the fuck.
只要... 只要能帮你摆脱困境就行
Just, uh, just help you out.
显然 我总是很高兴
O... Obviously, I'm always pleased
听取你的见解
to get your insights,
但是 我应该和哪一位谈
but, like, who am I talking to?
两位联合...
Co...
首席运营官
COOs.
你们俩谁说了算
Who's in charge here?
我弟弟和我有共同的责任
My brother and I have a joint responsibility.
你懂的 我们分担责任
You know, we're sharing duties,
但是我们在行事方面是一致的 对吧 罗曼
but we're on the same page operationally. Right, Rome?
我他妈的不知道他在说什么
I don't know what the fuck he's talking about.
只是 呃
There's just, uh,
现在氛围很是剑拔弩张
a lot of, uh, crackle in the air right now.
代理权争夺带来的外部压力
External pressures with the proxy battle,
-整个...  -是的
- that whole... - Yeah.
所以你是在拆除你埋下的炸弹
So you're defusing the bomb you planted.
是的 很确切 看到没 他明白了 他明白
Yes, precisely. See, he gets it. He sees.
我们只是来这里进行常规检查
We're just here for a routine health check.
就这些
That's all this is.
是谁做的决定
Where's this coming from?
-我们做的决定  -我爸做的决定
- It's coming from us. - It's coming from Dad.
不 我们为什么要围着这个话题
No. What, why are we dancing around this?
我爸做的决定 老爸对你不放心
It's coming from Dad. Dad's worried about you.
好的
Okay.
拜托 你也知道他是怎样的人
I mean, come on, you know how he is.
他跟不上时代 他在菲律宾还有一家工厂
He doesn't get it. He still has a plant out in the Philippines
在制造施乐的复印机呢
manufacturing Xerox machines.
但是他真他妈的精明
But he's fucking shrewd.
而且 现在...
And, right now...
现在 他的独眼巨人的巨眼
right now, his giant cyclops eye
正朝着这个方向看 他对这里的感觉就像
is looking in this direction, and he's feeling like
也许他买了一大堆垃圾
maybe he bought a giant pile of bullshit.
所以我现在来这里
So now here I am
尽可能以最礼貌的方式询问
to enquire in the politest terms possible
他妈的是怎么回事
what the fuck is going on.
我爸认为你可能耍了他
Dad thinks maybe you fucked him.
你收购我们时 我们的经营很稳固
Our numbers were solid when you bought us,
现在也很稳固
and they're solid now.
伙计 真的 这不是针对你
Dude, really, don't take it personally.
爸爸认为每个人都在耍他
Dad thinks everyone's fucking him.
我知道你诚实可靠
I know you're on the level.
帮我让他看清楚这一点吧
Help me make him see that.
你需要什么
What do you need?
我需要数据记录 我需要绩效指标
I need metrics, I need KPIs,
而且 我还需要一间办公室
and, uh, I need an office.
我也是 我也需要一间办公室
Me too, I need an office as well.
和他的分开 更好
Separate from his. Nicer.
开始了 我和皮奇竞争
It's on, me versus the Peach.
好的 我要...
Okay, I'm gonna s...
我要用我的大香肠甩她一脸
I'm gonna swing the old meat mallet.
我一上位就要碾压她
I'm gonna sit on her right out of the box.
所以 我可能会需要
Okay, so I could be calling
一点点沙袋[出气筒]
for a little bit of the old punch-bagging,
好吗 哥们
okay, buddy?
-嗯  -准备好玩沙包了吗
- Uh-huh. - Ready to play the bag?
-是的... 是的 是的 给我吧  -好的
- Y... Yeah, yeah. Give it to me. - Okay.
怎么了
What?
怎么了 格雷格
What is it, Greg?
在泛美网络科技上班 你知道吗 它有点像是
Being in at ATN, you know, it's kinda like
我不想做的事情之一
the one thing I didn't wanna do.
哦 好的 所以呢...
Oh, okay. So, what...
我应该把你留在公园部门消沉吗
Should I have left you at Parks to sink?
这...
I mean, it's...
这可是泛美网络科技啊 伙计 这是他妈的新闻
it's ATN, man. It's the fuckin' news.
-我知道  -这是洛根的G点
- I know. - It's Logan's G-spot.
我可以整夜指奸他
I can finger-bang him all night long.
我是最直接的下属 直接向他汇报 怎么了
I'm a direct direct report. What?
当然 只是...
Sure, just...
泛美网络科技
ATN?
这里...有点...
It's... It's like...
-有点违背我的原则  -你有原则
- kind of against my principles. - Your principles?
格雷格 别混蛋了 你哪有什么原则
Greg, don't be an asshole. You don't have principles.
兄弟 泛美网络科技是一种非常有毒的文化元素
Dude, ATN is a very toxic element in the culture.
你认真的吗 好吧 说一个你遵守的原则
Oh, seriously? Okay, name me one principle that you have.
我不知道 比如 我反对种族主义
I don't know, like, I'm against racism.
废话 我也反对种族主义 每个人都反对种族主义
Bullshit. I'm against racism. Everybody's against racism.
还有什么
What else?
-比如 不说谎  -滚开
- Like, don't lie. - Fuck off.
-比如 如果你搞新闻 你...  -滚开
- Like, if you're the news, you... - Fuck off!
-那是你的原则吗  -是啊 老兄
- That's your principle? - Yeah, dude.
格雷格 这早就不是他妈的查尔斯·狄更斯的旧世界了 好吗
Greg, this is not fucking Charles Dickens world, okay?
我们不会再四处谈论原则
You don't go around talking about principles.
我们都在努力做正确的事
We're all trying to do the right thing,
我们当然是
of course we are.
得了吧 伙计
But come on, man!
你他妈成熟点
Man the fuck up!
好吧 我成熟了 伙计
Okay, I am manned, man.
悉德来了
Here comes Cyd.
嘿 悉德 大名鼎鼎的皮奇
Hey, Cyd! The Peach!
传奇人物啊
The legend!
哦 汤姆
Oh, Tom!
-汤姆  -嘿
- Tom! - Hey!
你能加入真好
It's great to have you aboard.
我知道这会是
I know that this is gonna be
真正富有成效的合作
a really productive collaboration.
我只是希望
I just hope
我们之间... 模糊的界线
that there's no... weirdness
不要发生什么怪事 好吗
with our fuzzy boundaries, right?
你在开玩笑吗 如果你... 如果你想走更快
Are you kidding? If you... If you wanna go fast,
那就自己走 如果你想走得更远 那就一起走
go alone. If you wanna go far, go together.
-对吧  -没错
- Right? - Exactly.
是啊
Yeah.
-来见见团队吧  -真了不起
- Come meet the team. - Amazing!
你想带队吗
You wanna lead in there?
才不想呢
Oh, fuck no.
-你来带 汤米  -好的
- You lead, Tommy. - Okay.
你介意我来个开门红吗
You mind if I big-ball the first one?
来嘛 自掘坟墓哟 伙计
Do it! Your funeral, buddy.
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you, thank you.
他有没有瞟一眼我的草稿
So did he actually even see my draft?
呃...没有
Uh... no.
最后 我只是想到 凯莉和我的草稿
In the end, I just thought the draft Kelly and I did
更有 养分
had more, uh, goodness.
比如呢...
As in... ?
比如我们的稿子有良好的品质
As in it had the quality of being good
而不是卑鄙的品质
rather than the attributes of being shitty.
嗯 多表扬凯莉 顺便告诉你
Um, just also re Kelly, little sidebar.
你能别告诉别人我们的事吗
Can you not tell people about us?
哦 根本没有"我们"
Oh, but there is no us.
对 我们曾经在一起过 而且问题是
Right. but there was an us, and the problem is,
我的妻子不知道这事
my wife doesn't know about it.
哦 我丈夫绝对知道这事
Oh, but my husband absolutely does know about it,
所以我猜 那是 那是你自己的问题
so I guess that's, what, it's your problem?
我们有过外遇
We had the affair.
我们没有商量过
We didn't have the conversation
要不要告诉别人我们外遇这事
about telling people we had the affair.
对不起 内特 你想和我开个电话会议
I'm sorry, Nate, did you want a conference call
讨论怎么告诉你妻子我们干过吗
to discuss how to tell your wife we fucked?
谢谢大家
Thank you, everyone.
伟大的事件 伟大的事件
Great event. Great event.
谢谢大家 非常感谢
Thank you, everyone, so much.
还有民意调查
And the polling!
天哪 没有人会因此忘乎所以
My God! I mean, nobody's getting carried away,
只是一组数字而已
just one set of numbers,
只是一组相当大的数字 对吧
one pretty big set of numbers. Right?
对 谢谢大家 谢谢你们证明了自己的信仰
Right, so thank you. And testament to your faith.
谢谢 请你们
Thank you. Please,
尽情享用这些...
indulge yourselves in some, uh,
面筋和融化的奶酪 有何不可呢
gluten and melted cheese. Why not?
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you, thank you.
嘿 呃 电话怎么样
Hey, uh, how was the call?
很好 他们可喜欢我了
Great. They're eating out of my ass crack.
还让我周末用他妈的喷气飞机
Offered me use of the fucking jet on the weekend.
呃 是的 我的意思是 法律部门不可靠
Uh, yeah, I mean, the legals are wonky
新闻媒体很糟糕 但是 尽管去吧
and the optics are shitty, but go ahead.
听着
Look.
你不会直接拒绝波音飞机这样的礼物
You don't look a gift Boeing in the teeth.
对吧 对吧
Right? Right?
-不会  -我会精神百倍
- No. - I'll be so much fresher.
请允许我们失陪一下 我要...
Excuse us for a second. I just wanna...
女士 听着
Ma'am, listen.
征途漫漫 所有的这一切
Long road to travel and all of that,
目标都是为了入主白宫
but the compass points to Pennsylvania Avenue.
我必须开始考虑会面
I have to start thinking about appointments.
我在考虑见白宫幕僚长
I'm thinking about Chief of Staff.
是啊
Yeah.
你能想象到 当他们看到
I mean, can you imagine the look of fear
你出现在他们身边的时候 眼睛里的恐惧表情吗
in their eyes when they see you coming at them?
那些肥胖的混蛋白人老头
Those corpulent old white fucks.
这个奖励如何
How's that for a carrot?
这里就是我们制造辩论议题的地方
So that's where we shape the debate.
哦 很酷嘛
Ooh, cool shit.
我喜欢辩论不断变形的方式
And I love the way the debate keeps on getting shaped
就像燃烧的十字架
like a burning cross.
你不认同我们的新闻价值观
You don't share our news values.
哦 我在开玩笑
Oh, I'm kidding.
我在开玩笑 我明白的 我来自中西部
I'm kidding. I get it. I'm from the Midwest.
你知道吗 我妈的朋友 德布 270斤重
You know, my mom's friend, Deb, weighs, like, 300 pounds,
她几乎对所有事情都很生气
and she's pissed as fuck about practically everything,
所以 你知道吗 相信我
so, you know, trust me,
我记住了 我知道了
I'm down. I get it.
此外 按照洛根的意思来 对吗
Besides, what Logan wants, Logan gets, right?
洛根没有设定我们的新闻议程
Logan doesn't set our news agenda.
哦 不 他当然没有
Oh. No, of course he doesn't.
我知道 这太奇怪了 对吧
I know, it's so weird, huh?
他碰巧拥有一家新闻公司
He happens to own a news company
他们表达的观点正好和他的想法一致
and they say exactly what he thinks.
如果洛根不得不告诉我
If Logan had to tell me
或者告诉我的任何一个新闻编辑
or any of my news editors
要怎么运行或应该采取什么观点
what to run or what the angle was,
那我们就完蛋了 事情不能这么办
we would be fucked. That is not how it works.
这不是精神控制
This isn't mind control.
我们雇用想在这里工作的人
We hire people who want to work here.
我们服务的观众群体
and we serve a demographic
是非常非常聪明的一群人
of highly, highly intelligent viewers,
他们真的受够了
who are really tired
被别的地方那些喝着拿铁
of being patronized elsewhere
花着几百块钱做头发的混蛋们
by latte-sipping douchebags
颐指气使地对待
with hundred-dollar haircuts.
你的职位头衔很酷
You've got the cool job title,
你有行动的自由
you've got freedom of movement.
为什么换个更舒适的角度看待这里呢
Why don't you take a look somewhere more comfy?
就为了娱乐吗
Entertainment?
因为这才是关键所在
'Cause this is where the action is.
这里是利润中心
This is the profit center.
我们观众的平均年龄是68岁
The median age of our audience is 68.
广告都是成人纸尿裤和治疗便秘的药
The ads are all adult diapers and shit pills.
我们在新闻演示中的领先优势已经减半
Our lead in the news demo has halved.
你知道吗 也许我可以
You know, maybe I can
帮忙看看其中的一些
lend a hand to take a look at some of that.
你知道吗
You know,
他每隔四年就会安排一个人给我
he sends me one of you every four years.
-这个安排从没变过  -有趣
- That train is never late. - Interesting.
告诉我 他安排过来的其他人
And tell me, these others that he sends,
他们也是他的女婿吗
were they his son-in-law too?
我很好奇
I'm curious.
效率 悉德 我是来这里修剪赘肉的
Efficiencies, Cyd! I'm here to trim the flab.
你跟洛根说过这个吗
Have you told Logan this?
我监管收支 悉德
I spy savings, Cyd.
哦 好 汤姆
Oh, good, Tom.
非常好
That's very good.
因为这里经营得非常良好
Because I run a pretty tight ship.
所以...
So...
祝你好运
good luck to you.
我相信你让他非常非常兴奋
I'm sure you've got him very, very excited.
希望你能履行好自己的职责
I hope you can deliver.
好...
Well...
非常感谢你
Thank you very much.
还有 呃 去你的
And, uh, fuck you.
还有 呃 稍后再谈
And, uh, I'll catch up with you later.
谈你个死人头 傻逼
Not on your dying day, baby.
格雷格 我需要你去实地行动
Greg, I need you on the ground.
-哦  -好吗
- Oh. - Okay?
我需要你成为我的代表
I need you to be my representative on earth.
我想要你... 我希望你为我执行任务
I want you to... I want you to go on a mission for me
寻找泛美网络科技的隐私
and body-shame ATN,
找到臃肿的部位并指出来
find the fat and point it out.
怎么做呢 比如
Yeah, like, how?
比如 找出冗余人员 好吗
Like, find the excess, okay?
找出无关的丹麦劳工 多余的常驻人员
Find the extraneous Danish, the surfeit of stationary,
懒惰的清洁工 走路缓慢的邮件人
the... the lazy cleaner, the mail guy who walks slow.
好吗 把废物 笨蛋都清理出来
Okay? Snuffle out waste, pig man.
懂吗 我撑门面 你搞地下工作
Okay, I'll do the penthouse, you do the basement.
-行吗  -是的 好的 我明白了
- All right? - Yeah, yeah, you got it.
等等 呃 这些是什么
Wait, uh, which are these?
你知道吗 我也不确定
You know what? I'm not sure.
我来看看
Let me go check.
继续拿文件过来 他妈的把他淹死在文件堆里
Keep it coming. Fuckin' drown him in paper.
晚安 肯德尔
Good night, Kendall.
晚安 老兄
Night, dude.
他在做什么
What's he doing?
我不知道 读文件吧
I dunno. Reading?
谢谢 这回答没用
Thanks, useless.
喝你的冰沙 闭嘴
Drink your smoothie and shut up.
其实 喝冰沙...
Actually drinking the smoothie...
我只有52秒时间
I can give you 52 seconds.
好吧 我在沃尔特公司
Well, I'm in at Vaulter.
所以呢
Yeah, so?
所以 帮我赢过肯德尔啊
Yeah, so, let's fucking game this out.
罗曼 我们正在打代理权之战
Roman, we are in a proxy war.
飞机刚刚被劫持
The plane has just been hijacked,
所有发动机都掉进大海里了
all the engines have fallen into the sea,
飞行员的头发着火了
and the pilot's hair is on fire.
格丽 拜托 我需要点材料
Gerri, come on, I need something.
肯德尔正在干活
Kendall's doing shit.
不如这样吧 你也干活
Okay, how about this: you do shit.
你有些什么
What have you got?
一个想法 转向视频
One idea: pivot to video?
这个 他们已经尝试过了
Yeah, they tried that already.
你能过来吗 我想要你来我办公室商量
Can you just come over? I want you in the room.
我可以过来吗
Can I come over?
是啊 可能... 是啊...
Yeah. Could... Yeah...
操你妈的
Fuck you!
Fuck you.
不好意思 伙计们 你们有没有兴趣和我一起
Excuse me, folks, um, could I maybe interest you all
去喝一杯像洗车时流出来的
in going for one of those fuckin'...
污水一样的酒
IPAs that looks like run-off at the carwash?
他在椅子上吗
Is he in the chair?
嘿 爸
Hey, Dad?
我需要三个有主见的女人 都有谁
I need three independent women. Know any?
董事会里吗
The board?
如果坐轮椅的那个还在就好了[第一季的董事会成员 伊罗娜]
Be great if one was in a fucking wheelchair.
黑人 白人 新手 同性恋 都行
Black, white, green, pink.
柬埔寨地雷受害者 如果你认识的话
A Cambodian landmine victim, if you know any.
是的 成为你想要在世界上看到的改变
Yeah, be the change you wanna see in the world.
爸爸 你是真正的希望灯塔
You're a real beacon of hope, Dad.
你怎么看待皮尔斯
What do you think about Pierce?
收购吗  买下来作为一种防御吗
Buying? PGM as a defense?
我...老实说 我认为那不切实际
I... Honestly, I think that's chasing the white whale.
还是这个看法
Again.
它永远不会起作用 不适合
It's never gonna work, it's not a good fit.
嗯
Uh-huh.
爸爸 我在想 我们是不是应该...
Dad, I was wondering whether we should...
谈谈
talk.
你知道 关于...
You know, about...
之前的事不是梦 对吗
It wasn't a dream, right?
你在开玩笑吗 我很兴奋呢
Are you kidding? I'm excited!
那我们谈谈吧
So, let's talk.
你先说 还是我先说
Should you go, or shall I?
呃 我有一些想法 我...
Uh, well, I have some ideas that I...
西沃恩 真是惊喜啊 他都没告诉我
Siobhan? What a surprise. He never said.
-嗨  -嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
只是临时来的
Just a pop-in.
小家伙在告诉我 嗯...
Pinkie was telling me how, um...
康纳搬进了城里的一家酒店
Connor's moved into a hotel in the city.
我看见了
I saw.
他把所有的照片都群发出去了
He sent out his email bulletin with all the photographs.
他租了个房间 租了个女孩
He rents a room, he rents a girl.
你能查下理查德有没有关了那个该死的排名查询网站
Can you check if Richard's turned off that fuckin' Alexa?
不只是关掉 是彻底下线了
Not just off, unplugged.
即使贝索斯没在这 我身边的间谍还是很多
I've got enough spies after me without Bezos in here too.
好吗
Okay?
好的
Right.
那...
So...
我是这么看的
here's how I see it.
进公司
Come in.
和格丽共事半年 和卡尔共事半年
Six months with Gerri, six months with Karl.
再去香港工作个一年
Hong Kong for, say, another 12.
柏林 或者伦敦
Uh, Berlin, or London.
管理培训计划半年
Management training program for six.
然后回来 花一年时间和我一起
Come back, spend 12 months alongside me.
等你准备好了 我就放手
And when you're ready, I'll step aside.
哇 爸爸 那是很多年了
Wow, Dad, that's a lot of months.
要有一定的资历才合适
It's an appropriate amount of months.
还有 管理培训计划
Also, management training program?
罗曼当首席运营官
Roman's COO.
你让一个路都走不顺溜的小毛孩
You have a toddler with a hard-on
当首席运营官
for chief operating officer,
却让我去参加管理培训计划
and I'm going through a management training program?
你是个年轻女性 没有经验
You're a young woman with no experience.
我是女性 这是减分项
A woman. That's a minus.
嗯 这他妈当然是减分项
Well, of course it's a fucking minus!
世道又不是我定的
I didn't make the world!
但也受到了你的部分影响
You make a small part of it.
如果你不接受这个方案 你想怎样
If that doesn't work for you, what does?
那是他妈的... 那是三年的时间啊
That's a fucking... That's a three-year timeline.
好吧
Okay.
要不你明天过来
So why don't you come in tomorrow
陪我一天吧
and spend the day with me?
哦 我的天啊 爸
Oh, Jesus Christ, Dad.
怎么了
What?
我需要时间 我... 我还没有告诉过汤姆
I need time, I... I haven't even told Tom yet.
-告诉他啊  -还有吉尔那边
- Tell him. - And there's Gil.
我有自己的工作 不能就这么跑来找你
I have a job, I can't just come running to you.
怎么回事 西沃恩 到底是太慢了还是太快了
What is it, Siobhan, too slow or too fast?
因为我他妈的很困惑
Because I'm fucking confused.
爸爸 我想要这个
Dad, I want this.
只是过程需要商榷
It's just about the process.
好的
Okay.
是吗
Okay?
那么...你想好好谈下吗
So... you wanna get into it?
现在不要
Not now.
我很忙 股东委托书
I'm busy. Proxy statement.
你又没有提前告诉我
You didn't give me any warning.
-行  -我的意思是 这样
- All right. - I mean, you know,
明天晚上可以吗
tomorrow night could work?
-那...可以吗  -明天吗
- That... Yeah. - Tomorrow?
呃...好吧 我看看
Uh... Yeah, let me take a look.
哦 时间不合适吗
Oh, is that no good for you?
我住在附近
I'm around.
-我很兴奋  -嗯嗯
- I'm excited. - Mm-hmm.
我也是
Me too.
我明天会告诉你...
I'll get back to you tomorrow...
-董事会的人的名单  -嗯嗯
- on the names for the board. - Mm-hmm.
-爱你  -我爱你 晚安
- Love you. - I love you. Goodnight.
好了
All right.
我时间有限
I haven't got all day.
议程是沃尔特
Agenda is Vaulter.
我们需要在两天之后的投资人会议之前
We need a way forward on the Vaulter problem
找到解决沃尔特公司的办法
ahead of investor meetings in two days' time.
你们想一起陈述还是...
Do you want to present jointly or... ?
肯
Ken?
嗯 我来吧
Yeah, I'll take it.
嗯 那 我花了36个小时
Um, so, I've spent the last 36 hours
深入了解了业务的驱动因素
on a deep dive into the drivers of the business.
先说结论 这是个万人坑
Headline is, it's a body pit.
他们有海量的数据 却没有分析
Uh, they have mass of data with no analytics.
没有办法分辨哪儿是哪儿
There's no way of telling what's a hand and what's a foot.
但这仍然是一个重量级的业务
But it's still a killer business.
平台 品牌
The platform, the brands.
呃 社会思潮和文化占据了领先优势
Uh, ethos and culture are leading edge.
而且 嗯 在我看来 问题可以解决
And, um, in my view, it's fixable.
这些混球总是想试探底线
It's funny how these fuck-ups
真他妈搞笑
always make the bottom line look fatter.
他们只是需要有人指导
All they need is adults in the room.
会计团队 分析团队
Accounting team, analytics team,
还有 呃 投资
and, uh, investment.
这些年我们耗费了5000万
We burn 50 million for a few years,
我们...让它成为了世界上最好的东西
we... make it the best thing in the world.
哦 是这样吗
Oh, is that all?
好吧 你总是说"花钱才能办事"
Well, you always say "Gotta burn to turn."
罗慕路斯 你查到些什么
Romulus, what's your read?
你知道吗 有趣的是 爸爸
You know, it's interesting, Dad,
因为我听到他说的这些
because I hear everything that he's saying,
实际上...几乎像是一番有内涵的话
and it actually... It almost sounds like a good pitch.
但是... 我觉得是瞎扯
But... I call bullshit.
我花了一些时间在那里 但是我没看到他说的这些
I spent some time down there, and I'm just not seeing it.
现在 我不确定他们在做什么
Now, I don't know exactly what they're doing,
但他们都是些假货
but they're fakes.
他妈的蜂箱 杏仁奶 还有...
Fucking beehives, almond milk, and...
"再花一个星期写那份报告 玛蒂尔达"
"Take another week on that report, Matilda."
感觉就不对劲
It smells wrong,
他们在遮掩
and they're hiding shit.
说到遮掩
Speaking of hiding shit,
我带了几个他们的工作人员出去玩
I took a couple of their staffers out,
我灌得他们烂醉如泥
I got them shitfaced,
显然
and apparently,
他们希望成立工会
they're looking to unionize,
而且他妈的很快就会成立
and fucking soon.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
支付透明度
Pay transparency,
讨价还价的权利
bargaining rights.
就是些肮脏混乱的屁事
Just nasty, tangly shit.
这不是万人坑
And it's not a body pit,
不管他妈的万人坑是什么东西
whatever the fuck a body pit is.
这是他妈的牛奶什锦早餐坑
It's a fucking muesli pit,
而且不符合我们的核心 你知道...
and doesn't fit with our core, you know...
价值
values.
所以现在我在想 直接关掉这个操蛋的公司得了
So now I'm thinking we just shutter the fucker.
关掉 这想法太棒了
Close it? That's chunky.
得了... 他都不知道自己在说什么
Come... I mean... He doesn't know what he's talking about.
他脑子有点疯
That's just insane.
调低账面价值会怎么样 这个苦果只能吞了
The write-down on that would be what? It's a bitter pill.
得了 现在正在进行代理权争夺战
Come on, I mean, i... i... in the middle of a proxy fight
斯图威和桑迪拿下了"华尔街日报"的整版广告
when we've got Stewy and Sandy taking out full-page ads
正在抨击我们把资本弄得一团糟
in the Journal attacking us for pissing capital up the wall?
那 那样会让我们看起来很虚弱
It... It... I mean, it makes us look weak.
不 这会让我们看起来很无情
No, it makes us look ruthless.
而且 实际上 我确实知道我在说什么
And actually, I do know what I'm fucking talking about.
爸 我们他妈的在做什么
Dad, what the fuck are we doing?
让我看看这家公司其他地方的增长
Show me the bloat anywhere else in this company.
在哪里 你告诉我
Where is it? You show me.
告诉我
Show me the waste
我们让这些黑客逍遥法外所造成的浪费
that we're letting these fuckers get away with.
很好 那我们把他们重组 然后再发展...
Fine, so we restructure them and we grow them...
我想 如果我们不关掉这公司 我们就把它重组
I think if we don't shutter it, then we gut it.
我们像雕刻南瓜一样把这个狗屎公司拆分了
We carve that shit like a pumpkin.
怎么拆分
How?
你把利润中心分离出来
You hive off the profit center,
保留域名 档案
you keep the domain name, the archive,
嗯...
um...
全拆散 爸
Gut level, Dad,
这事没有转圜余地 他们都是些混蛋
this thing is not coming back. They're fuckin' assholes.
爸
Dad.
沃尔特可以成为我们的标杆
Vaulter can be our lodestar.
现... 现在不是撤退的时候
Th... This is... This isn't the time to retreat.
你弟弟说得对 拆分吧
Your brother's right. Gut it.
好的
Okay.
罗曼
Roman,
我希望你和格丽一起加入代理权争夺战
I want you on the proxy battle with Gerri.
肯德尔
Kendall,
你能为我重组沃尔特吗
you think you can gut Vaulter for me?
还是说你需要帮手
Or you need help?
爸爸 我会处理好的
I'll take care of it, Dad.
你知道吗 威拉告诉我
Uh, you know, when Willa told me
要为了她的戏剧搬来纽约住的时候
about moving to New York for her play,
我想 "啊 我不想搬到这个城市
I thought, "Ah, I don't want to move to the city.
我想留在牧场
I wanna stay on the ranch.
也许我会找个新女朋友"
Maybe I'll get me a new girlfriend."
我开玩笑呢
I'm kidding.
不 他说的是真的
No, I mean, it's true.
要把老人从甜点中哄出来相当困难
It was pretty hard to wheedle the old man out of the dessert.
但是 嗯 我们现在在这里
But, um, we're here now
在我们这个不那么卑微的家里...
in our, um, not-so-humble home...
酒店里 嗯
hotel. Um.
但是 呃 朋友们 亲人们 欢迎
But, uh, friends, family, please,
随时来探访我们
you know, feel free to drop in anytime,
而且 嗯 不用担心这些花销
and, um, don't worry about all this,
因为我们会买单 所以...
'cause it's on our tab. So...
好的 真棒
Okay. Great.
干杯
Cheers!
好的
Okay.
嘿 老康 非常感谢你
Hey, Con, thank you so much
安排这些汉堡和所有这些狗屁招待
for taking care of the sliders and all this shit.
是的 还有香槟 你真是太好了
Yeah, and the champagne. It's very big of you.
我也喜欢你这里还没有装修的那些地方
And I love what you haven't done with the place as well.
嗯 你知道吗 我们做了一笔很好的交易
Yeah, well, you know we got a really good deal.
而且 戏剧排练就要开始了
And rehearsals are right around the corner.
另外 我也需要在城里找个落脚点
Plus, I needed a place in the city
因为我很快就会开始加速了
'cause I'm gonna start ramping up soon.
所以我需要竞选总部
So I needed campaign headquarters.
等等
Wait.
-你没事吧  -是的 我没事
- You okay? - Yeah, I'm fine.
-你还在筹备那事吗  -非常好笑 是的
- Are you still doing that? - Very funny. Yes.
我还在申请
I'm still applying for the job
美国总统这份工作
of President of the United States.
哦 真有你的
Oh, good for you.
是啊 你呢...
Yeah. Do you...
你觉得这就像是自然发展一样吗
Do you think that that's like a natural progression
从"从来没有做过任何事 从没做过"
from "never done nothing, never,"
到"要做世界上最重要的工作"
to "most important job in the world?"
-好吧...  -比如 你也许
- Well... - Like, could you maybe
应该先获得一些资历这样吧
get a little experience at, like at a CVS, something, first?
是的 是的 就像在桥下面那种廉价的打飞机
Yeah, yeah, or just, like, nickel hand jobs under a bridge.
-从小事开始  -你们给我制定了一个大计划啊
- Start small. - You guys have big plans for me.
那地方就像是停留在过去[时间机器]
Place is a time machine.
每次他们需要文件磁带时 就要花费45分钟
It's like 45 minutes every time they need file tape,
从公司到皇后区的某个仓库取
all the way to some warehouse in Queens.
好的 所以呢
Okay, so?
所以 我不知道 我的意思是...
So, I don't know. I mean...
为什么没有数字化
How come it isn't digitized?
整个泛美网络科技 完全用的是模拟信号 汤姆
The whole of ATN, it's totally analog, Tom.
所以 我可以解雇人喽
So I could fire people?
对吧 如果我们这样做 如果我们数字化
Correct? If we did this? If we digitized?
我... 你可以去掉
I... I mean, you'd be removing, like,
每个节目的制作环节中的两个环节
two links from the production chain of every show.
-但是 那样会不会...  -好的 好的 好的
- But would it be... - Okay, okay, okay.
但是...但就人头数而言
But... but in terms of skulls,
你觉得有多少人头
how many skulls, do you think?
-我们可以裁掉的人头吗  -是的
- That we can lose? - Yeah.
我不知道 我...我猜 估计有30或50个
I dunno. I... I guess, like, 30 or 50?
50个人吗
Fifty skulls?
我流口水了 猪头
I'm slavering, pig man!
50个人是很多人啊
Fifty skulls is a lot of skulls!
是啊
Yeah.
我知道 是... 那是...很多人
I know, it's goo... It's... tons.
哦 看看这个混蛋
Oh, look at this fuckin' prick.
哎呀 我都快为他感到难过了
Yikes, I almost feel sorry for him.
是吗 为什么
Oh yeah? Why?
刚刚丢掉自己的男子汉气概
Just emptied the contents of his scrotum
跪倒在爸的脚下
at Dad's feet.
我们正在重组沃尔特
We're gutting Vaulter.
-是吗  -是的
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
这是个好主意吗
Is that a good idea?
他妈的好得不能再好了
Fucking great idea.
这是肯德尔的宝贝 现在我们要把它毁之一炬
It's Kendall's baby, and now we're gonna burn it.
嘿 嗯...所以 我们在想 呃...
Hey, um... So, we we're thinking, uh...
我 呃 塔比莎和我
me and, uh, Tabitha and I,
呃 我们想邀请你和汤姆共进晚餐
uh, that we'd like to have you and Tom over for dinner.
呃...对不起 什么 你...
Uh... sorry, what? Do you...
罗曼·罗伊 你刚刚邀请我们吃晚饭吗
Roman Roy, did you just invite us to dinner?
噢 去你的 好吧 闭嘴
Oh, fuck you. All right, shut up.
是的 我邀请了 装什么样子嘛
Yes, I did. Metro poser bullshit.
吃吃饭 聊聊天
Napkins and chitchat.
哦 谈谈种族关系 吃点羽衣甘蓝
Ooh, race relations. Kale.
嘿
Hey.
你觉得 如果我打电话给客房服务
Do you reckon if I called room service
然后要求他们捅我的眼睛 他们会照做吗
and asked them to poke me in the eye, they would?
待在里面真是难以忍受
It's pretty unbearable in there.
能给我吸一口吗
Can I get a drag?
嗯
Yeah.
我听说爸要拿沃尔特开刀
I hear Dad's got Vaulter in a crosshair.
罗曼说的吗
Roman?
他不应该和你谈论这件事的
He shouldn't be talking to you about that.
在我看来 这步棋下得很糟糕
Just seems like a bad move to me.
我只是说 我一直很喜欢它
I'm just saying, I always liked it.
嗯 好吧
Yeah, well.
爸是对的
Dad's right.
你同意他的看法吗
Are you with him on this?
他看到了一切 小西
He sees everything, Shiv.
你很难找到一个折衷的方式
You have a hard time finding a happy medium
在崇拜他和想要杀死他之间找到平衡
between worshipping him and wanting to kill him.
-沃尔特公司这事  -嗯
- The Vaulter thing. - Mm.
分拆重组
Gutting it.
要是这决定错了怎么办
What if it's the wrong thing?
我还以为爸同意你的意见呢
I thought your dad agreed with you?
呃 是的 他是同意 现在他们正在分拆
Uh, yeah, he did. And now they're doing it.
他们实际上正在照我说的做
They're actually doing the thing that I said.
他妈的
Fuck.
或许你是胜任了工作呢
Think maybe you just did your job.
我们可以再来点香槟吗
Shall we get some more champagne?
我意思是...
I mean...
这样可能是对的 有可能不对 但也可能对
It could be right. It might not be, but it could be.
也许我很聪明呢
Maybe I'm smart.
当然
Sure.
也许
Maybe.
你做了一件事
You did a thing.
祝你走运
Mazel tov.
你知道吗 我要...
You know, I'm gonna...
我要和你爸约个时间
I'm gonna schedule some time with your dad,
请他出去吃饭 请他喝酒 和他一起吃饭
and take him out for dinner and wine him and dine him
把我的想法灌进他脑子里 你知道吗
and make love to him with my ideas, you know?
这可能会很重大 小西
This could be huge, Shiv.
汤姆 我想...
Tom, I think...
我想我们应该谈谈
I think we should talk.
你想离开这里吗
You wanna get out of here?
好的
Okay.
是关于泛美网络科技吗
Is this about ATN?
嘿 你... 你想喝点什么吗
Hey, you... you want something?
我帮你倒点
I'll get you something.
哦 看来是大件事
Ooh, that's a biggie.
是关于安排方面的吗
Is this about the arrangement?
听着 汤姆 是...
Look, Tom, it's...
不 是关于韦斯达
no, it's Waystar.
这事永远不会发生
This is never gonna happen,
我根本就不相信他 而且 就算我答应了
and I don't even trust him, and even if I did,
我也根本不确定自己想不想要它
I'm not even sure that I would want it.
但是 呃...
But, uh...
他把公司给我了
he offered it to me.
做接班人
To be next.
爸
Dad.
哦
Oh.
-哦 我的天...  -嗯
- Oh my... - Mm.
小西 ...什么时候的事
Shiv... when?
呃 汉普顿的时候
Uh, the Hamptons.
汉普顿的时候
The Hamptons?
哦 天哪 小西 那是...
Oh, my God, Shiv, that's...
那是一个星期前啊
That's like a week ago.
恭喜 卧了个槽
Congratulations! What the fuck!
我知道
I know!
我...我...我不知道该怎么想
I mean, I... I... I don't know what to think.
天哪 这...
Holy shit! I mean,
这... 太重大了
this is... huge!
所...
S...
-所以 你呢...  -我想要吗 不想
- So, I mean, do you... - Want it? No!
而且我根本就不相信他 所以我...
And I don't even trust him, so I...
因为我以为这是
Because I thought that it was something
我们希望...
that we wanted for me...
-的确是  -...我来得到的
- We do. - ... to have it?
-的确是  -那是...我的意思是
- We do! - That was... I mean,
那只是计划
that was just the plan.
计划...仍然是那样的
That's st... still the plan.
我只是计划的一个修改
Me is just a modification of the plan.
对 当然
No, sure.
这是...相当大的一个修改
It's q... quite a big modification.
但是... 那...
But d... d... so, did...
那...那他...
d... did he...
我们...呃 跟我描绘下 他是怎么...
We... Uh, paint the picture for me. What'd he...
他问我 我就答应了
He asked me, and I said yes.
但只是作为预案
But only as a play.
绝对是
Totally.
那预案是什么
So what was the play?
好吧 他之前就问过我 很显然
Well, he's asked before, obviously,
而这一次是真的...
and this time was real...
所以...
so...
我想 如果我拒绝 我会失去影响力
I thought I would be deleveraging power if I said no.
是的 没错
Exactly. Yes.
汤姆 这事百分之百不会发生
Tom, this is 100 percent not going to happen.
但是 接受才是明智的 对吗
But it's smart to say yes, right?
我太...
I am so...
为你感到兴奋了
excited for you!
-谢谢  -为我们
- Thank you. - For us!
真的
I am.
你知道吗 如果你想要它 没问题的
And you know, it's okay for you to say that you want it.
我会支持你的
I'd support you.
好吧 听着...
Well, look, I mean...
如果我确实想要它 我...我...我没有
Say I did want it, w... and I... I don't,
你知道的 你...
you know, you...
如果我是韦斯达的总裁...
if I was CEO of Waystar, I mean...
亲爱的 你可就是有头有脸的重要人物啦
I mean, you, honey, are gonna be something huge.
是啊
Yeah.
当然 比如呢
Sure. Like what?
我... 我不知道
I... I don't know.
但我们会弄明白的
But we'll figure it out.
是的 那是为了以后的... 打算
Yeah, that's for later on down... down the road.
-无论何时 无论何时  -哇
- Whenever. Just whenever. - Wow.
这太搞了 对吧
I mean, it's hilarious, right?
哦 是的
Oh, yes!
这真他妈搞笑
It's fucking funny!
是啊...
Yeah...
-嘿 过来  -嘿
- Hey, come here. - Hey.
-嗯  -嘿
- Mm. - Hey.
哦 哦 现在吗
Oh. Oh, now?
-嗯 为什么不  -好吧 让我...
- Mm. Why not? - Well, let me just...
等等 我先去刷个牙
Hang on. Let me just go and brush my teeth.
不
No.
-不 过来  -好的
- No, come here. - Okay.
我... 我听说你哥要竞选总统
I... I hear your brother's running for president.
也许我们应该把他带来这里
Maybe we should get him here.
他看起来像是个... 严肃的人[此处是反话]
He seems like the... the serious one.
对 劳伦斯 我们有一个问题
Right. Lawrence, we have a problem.
好吗
Okay?
我爸想让你这儿关门
My dad wants to shut you down.
-你在说什么  -是的
- What are you talking about? - Yeah.
但是 我不想让你担心我爸
But I don't want you to worry about my dad.
好吗 我可以搞定我爸
Okay? I can handle my dad.
你他妈的在说什么啊
The fuck you talking about?
我知道这里是怎么回事
I know what's going on here.
好吗 这是...这只是一个波将金村庄[远看不错 近看只是个门面]
Right? It's a... It's a... It's a Potemkin village.
我的意思是 网站的参与度和跳出率
I mean, the engagement and bounce rate
都被夸大了 而且搞得一团糟
have been inflated and fucked around so much
他们无法验证
they're impossible to verify.
你的份额统计数据 ...客户流失量
your share stats, the... the churn,
搜索引擎流量 关键绩效都是瞎扯
the SEO traffic KPIs are all bullshit.
你坑了我 骗我收购了它
I mean, you suckered me in, and, uh, I bought it.
我们有几个月流量数据是很糟糕...
We had a couple shitty traffic months...
因为脸书改变了他们的算法
Uh, Facebook changed their algorithm.
嗯
Uh-huh.
-我们被玩弄了 好吗  -行
- We got face-fucked, okay? - All right.
我们正在转折点开始回升了
We're turning the corner now.
好的
Okay.
哦...好的
O... Okay.
什么 好吧 这...这是真的吗
What? Yeah, o... okay. Is... Is that real?
-洛根的决定吗  -听着 我可以解决这个问题
- From Logan? - Look, I can fix this.
好吗 但是 不要再继续糊弄我了
Okay? But no more obfuscation.
不要再给我烂数据了
No more shitty data.
我需要完整 快速 清晰的数据
I need the full, fiber-optic, clear-channel shit.
完整地核查整个数据 我们快速行动
CT scan the whole place, and we move fast.
好的
Okay.
你喜欢背叛你爸吗
Do you like double-crossing your dad?
哦 那是你的最爱
Oh, that's your favorite.
不是吗
Isn't it?
我认为 我可以让他承认 自己犯了一个错误
I'm of the opinion he can be persuaded he's making a mistake.
-好吗  -好的
- Okay? - Okay.
哦 还有 还有一件事
Oh yeah, w... Uh, one more thing.
我...我...我需要大家在成立工会这事上冷静下来
I... I... I need everyone to cool it on unionizing.
好吧 他们不会放弃的
Okay, they're not gonna do that.
其中一半人即将签署工会卡
Half of them are about to sign union cards.
让我跟他们谈谈
Let me speak to them.
这里的每个人都他妈讨厌你
Everyone here fucking hates you.
我想我能接受
I think I can take it.
嘿 大家好 感谢...
Hey, everyone. Thanks for...
谢谢你们过来 一会儿就好
Thanks for gathering. This'll just be a minute.
你们...你们在后面的能听到吗
Can you... Can you guys hear me in the back?
能听到吗
Yeah?
呃...
Uh...
沃尔特
Vaulter.
嘿 嗯...好吧
Hey, um... Okay.
听着 你们有些人可能已经注意到了这一点
Look, some of you might have noticed this already,
但是 呃 我希望你们直接从我这儿得知这事
but, uh, just so you're getting it direct from me,
呃 过去一周以来 韦斯达管理层一直在
uh, Waystar management has been taking a look at the business
核查公司业务
over the last week.
但是 我想亲自对你们说...
But I just wanna say this to you in person...
我相信沃尔特是这家公司的未来
I believe Vaulter is the future of this company.
当然
Sure.
我很严... 我他妈...非常严肃
I'm Se... I'm fuckin' s... dead serious.
只是...你们不能质疑我对你们
Just... You can't question my belief
在这里建造的一切所具有的信念
in what you've all built here.
质疑...劳伦斯在这里建造的这一切
You know, in... in... in what Lawrence has built.
但是 如果我们要获得成功
But if we're gonna come through here,
我们就要看清脚下的路
we need to be light on our feet.
所以 我个人认为
That's why I personally think
你们创建工会是一个错误的决定
it would be a mistake for you to unionize.
先...先听我说完
Just... Just hear me out.
好的 我们会帮你们
Okay, we will get you
成立一个非常强大的独立仲裁小组
a really punchy independent arbitration panel,
我们会给你们加薪
we'll get you a pay bump.
我知道你们很多人在和工会眉目传情
I know a lot of you are flirting with the guild,
我只是请你们考虑一下
and I'm just asking you to consider
先终止行动
putting that on ice.
我们内部先努力把问题弄清楚
And let's try and figure this out inside.
我们把问题留在...
We keep it in the...
超他妈俗气的韦斯达家庭之内
fuckin' super cheesy, but in the Waystar family.
因为我们不想这里出现敌对的局面
'Cause we do not want an adversarial situation here.
好吗 我们想要沟通
Okay, we want communication,
我们想要协商
we want engagement.
让我们一起齐心协力
So let's all pull together
回到你们的办公桌
and go back to your desks
然后产生5个 10个 100个想法
and generate me five, ten, 100 ideas
告诉我和我身边这位伙计
and hit me and my man here up.
好吗
Okay?
谢谢大家
Thank you.
嗯 我不知道 斯坦利
Yeah, I don't know, Stanley.
我...我只是不知道我是否能够
I... I just don't know if I could ever
真的用上这个区域
practically make use of this area.
这只是一个夹层 你知道吗 只是一个附赠的空间
That's just a mezzanine. You know, it's just a bonus.
你有一间起居室 楼梯下面是储藏室
you have a... a living room with under-stair storage.
好吧 只不过...
Sure. It's just...
斯坦利 我最迫切需要储藏的东西
the thing I need storage for most urgently of all, Stanley,
是我自己
is me.
你懂吗 我...我需要...
You know? I'm... I need...
我需要空间安顿自己
I need storage for myself.
伙计 只是一张床而已
Dude, it's just a bed.
你想太多了吧
You're overthinking it.
肯德尔
Kendall?
完全没问题
Totally.
好的 现在出发
Yep, on my way.
怎么样
So?
考虑一下吧
It's a maybe.
嘿 肯
Hey, Ken?
喂
Yo.
嘿
Hey.
我拿到你要的了
I got the stuff.
-谢谢  -嗯
- Thank you. - Yeah.
所以 你觉得怎么样
So, what do you think?
呃 这个地方吗 我觉得...
Uh, of this? I think...
这里...
it's...
很大 这里 嗯 这里空间非常大
huge. It's, um, it's a very large space.
长度...长度是多少
What's the... what's the footage?
呃 我不知道
Uh, I don't know.
开发商高估了需求
Developers overestimated demand,
所以我把所有五个单位全买了 我的人会把它们倒卖掉
so I bought all five units and my guy's gonna flip 'em.
是的 因为这里...这里...
Yeah, 'cause i... it's...
空间非常长
an abundance of footage.
长得...有点尴尬了
An embarrassment of... of footage.
是啊
Yeah.
给你用
It's yours.
我...我的意思是 在卖出去之前
I... I mean, until the market starts to move,
-但是...  -在卖出去之前
- but... - Until it starts to move.
不 我是认真的
No, I'm serious.
-是的  -就像...
- Yeah. - Like...
是的 这里现在归你住了 格雷格
Yeah, you live here now, Greg.
好的
Okay.
呃 很酷 是啊
Uh, cool. Yeah.
我可以承受很多心理上的痛苦 所以...
I can take a lot in terms of psychological pain, so...
耶 酷毙了 我要住在这里了 太棒了
Yeah. Sweet, I live here! Nice.
我非常认真
I'm totally serious.
是的 我知道 我需要一个住的地方 所以...
Yeah, I know. I needed a place to live, so...
现在 呃 现在我明白了
Now, uh, now I got it!
呃 这是你的钥匙
Uh, here's your key.
在我招聘到楼下的门卫之前 钥匙都归你管
Until I get a doorman downstairs.
我不是在逗你
I'm not fuckin' around.
不过 房子里空空如也
Like, it's just gonna be empty.
-不算什么大忙  -肯德尔
- It's not a big deal. - Kendall.
什么 伙计
What, dude?
这里他妈的...这...这是...
This is fuck... Th... this is...
伙计 谢谢
Dude, thank you.
太感谢了 伙计
So much, man.
哇 我意思是...
Wow. I mean...
-看看这些天花板  -是的
- Look at these ceilings. - Yeah.
层高不错 还有大窗户
Nice height, you got big windows,
光线也很好
a lot of light.
嗯 你有过自己的房子吗
Yeah. Have you ever had your own place?
真他妈爽
Fuck yeah.
我想我们今晚可以聚聚
I was thinking we could hang out tonight.
-嗯  -比如 就在这里
- Yeah. - Like, in here.
-当然  -举办一个小派对
- Sure. - Have a little party.
酷毙了
Sweet.
嗨
Hi!
-嗨  -汤姆·万布斯甘斯
- Hi! - Tom Wambsgans.
嗨
Hi!
-男人的握手  -男人的握手
- Manly handshake. - Manly handshake.
-呃...  -我有一个...
- Uh... - I have this...
无法自制的冲动 想要么用膝盖顶着别人的阴道
overwhelming urge to either knee someone in the vagina
要么吐在地板上
or spit on the floor.
嗯 他今晚有点小紧张
Hmm. He's been a little bit nervous about tonight.
紧张 他妈的得了吧
Nervous, come the fuck on.
就因为这对暴露狂和性冷淡的无性夫妻吗
For din-dins with firecrotch and normcore?
拜托
Please.
好了 请进来吧
Well, come on in!
喝点香槟吧
Have some champagne.
享受我们美丽的房间
Enjoy our beautiful room.
可以在这里度过你的一生 这就是我的想法
Could spend your whole life here. That's how I figure it.
在沙发上出生 在这里火化
Born on the couch and cremated in here.
我可以喝健怡可乐吗
Can I get a Diet Coke?
哦 汤姆感冒了
Oh, Tom has a cold,
他希望每个人都知道
and he wants everyone to know.
哦
Oh.
好吧 我们可以派人去买一些生理盐水
Well, we could send out for some saline,
我们可以站在一旁 看着你冲洗鼻子
we could stand around and watch you do a nasal wash.
不 不 谢谢 我很好 谢谢
No, no. thank you. I'm good. Thank you.
我听到一些关于我们兄弟的故事
I'm hearing some stories about that brother of ours.
显然...
Apparently...
你真的想喝那个吗 因为我还有更烈的酒
You wanna actually drink that? 'Cause I got some stronger shit.
-是的  -你喜欢日本威士忌吗
- Yeah. - Do you like Japanese whiskey?
-是的  -我有一种酒
- Yeah. - I've got this one
味道喝着就像他妈的龙尿...
that tastes like fucking dragonpiss...
你应该试着吃点东西
You should try swallowing something.
比如蜂蜜
Like honey.
我很好 谢谢你
I'm fine, thank you.
据说他又在搞动作了
Word is he's on maneuvers again.
做出各种各样的承诺 以保证沃尔特继续运营
Making all kinds of promises about keeping Vaulter open.
什么 爸知道吗
What? Does Dad know?
呃 不 爸不知道
Uh, hell no, Dad doesn't know.
他是个诡计多端的混蛋
He's a shenaniganizing piece of shit.
但是 我脑子里不断想着的是...
But the thing I keep turning over in my mind is...
我要告诉爸爸吗
do I tell Dad?
因为如果我现在对肯落井下石
Because if I drop the shoe on Ken now,
他这辈子就彻底废了
he's crushed forever.
呃...
Uh...
如果肯德尔我行我素 那么... 随他吧
If Kendall's going rogue, then... let him.
迟早 会溅得他满脸脏
Sooner or later, it's gonna blow up in his face.
我就喜欢看人脸上溅脏水
I love it when it blows up in people's faces.
-是的  -没错 这他妈是我最喜欢的
- You do. - I do. It's my fuckin' favorite.
我喜欢现在这样的方式
I like how this is working.
我们 我在这里看到了未来
Us. I see a future here.
是啊 当然
Yeah. Sure.
-不 我也是  -是的
- No, me too. - Yeah.
因为 你知道吗 现在有个良机
'Cause, you know, there's an opening.
嗯 知道吗 没有人觉得我会成功
Yeah, see, no one sees me coming.
但是我已经胜利在望了
But I am right on the shoulder.
如果爸爸明天宣布 他会宣布我
If Dad announces tomorrow, he announces me.
只能是我 没有别的选择
Has to, there's no other option.
我的意思是 这真他妈的疯了 但我是他最好的选择
I mean, it's fucking insane, but I am the best he's got.
是啊
Yeah.
除非... 还有另外一个人选
Unless... There is one other.
谁
Who?
小西 我应该担心汤姆吗
Shiv, should I be worried about Tom?
汤姆
Tom?
不 你不需要担心汤姆
No, you don't need to be worried about Tom.
好吧
Okay.
行
All right.
新闻部门怎么样 汤姆
How's news, Tom?
很有挑战性
Challenging.
日子有点难熬 但是 你知道的...
Tough row to hoe, but, you know...
我想我找到了出路
think I see a way out.
-很好 是的  -是吗
- It's good, yeah. - Yeah?
出路 好样的 伙计
A way out. Good for you, man.
那 是什么呢 你说的出路
So what is it, this way out?
噢 现在言之过早 我...嗯
Oh, it's early days, and I... Yeah.
我还没有和洛根讨论过 但...
I haven't even discussed it with Logan yet, but...
哦 这是秘密吗
Oh, so it's a secret?
那太他妈刺激了
That's fucking exciting.
你什么时候告诉他 在外面留宿的时候吗[讽刺汤姆是小孩子]
When are you gonna tell him, at the sleepover?
嗯 不 不
Well, um, no.
我们正在调查...嗯 我正在调查
We're-looking in... Well, I'm looking into
将泛美网络科技数字化
digitizing ATN.
比如 把古老的模拟信号基础设施
Like, a total overhaul of the... of the legacy
全盘改造
analog infrastructure.
是啊
Yeah.
同时极大地提高生产力
Making a lot of productivity gains as well,
所以我觉得你爸会非常高兴
so I think your dad will be pretty pleased.
真他妈绝了
Fuckin' A.
看看这个"饲养器"
Look at the corn-feeder.
发挥了所有的协同作用
Going all synergies and shit.
-是的  -很好
- Yeah. - Nice.
值得一试
Worth a shot.
谢啦 兄弟
Thanks, man.
顺便问一下 汤姆 你在哪里买西装
Where do you buy your suits, by the way, Tom?
也许这就是
Like, maybe that's why
我动作不像你那么快的原因
I'm just not moving as fast as you.
我就是没有那种直筒短装夹克的公司形象
I just don't have that, like, boxy, corporate look.
对吧
Right?
我很抱歉 但是 就像
I mean, I'm sorry, but, like,
什么鬼 你看起来像个变形金刚
what the fuck? You look like a Transformer.
就像 你的身体有什么问题吗 伙计
Like, wh... what's wrong with your body, man?
罗曼 好了 他的身体没有任何问题
Rome, come on. There's nothing wrong with his body,
这他妈只是西装而已
it's just fuckin' suits.
怎么了 拜托 我们...我们以前也笑过的
What? Come on, we... we've laughed about it before.
-有吗  -是的
- You have? - Yeah.
他很节俭 而且他的西装品味最差
He's thrifty, and he has the worst taste in suits.
品味真的很烂...
Totally has terrible Ta...
你看起来就像双子城的离婚律师
You look like a divorce attorney from the Twin Cities.
部分原因是走路的姿势 就像一个真的...
It's partly the walk. It's like a real...
-机器人吗  -不 农民的步伐
- Robot? - No, agricultural walk.
农民的步伐
Agricultural walk!
你知道吗 我试过找给老爸定制西装的人
You know, I tried to get, uh, one of his suits tailored
-定制了一套给他  -嗯嗯
- by the guy that Dad uses. - Mm-hmm.
-但他穿起来非常...就像...  -嘿 小西 够了啦
- But he just looked so, like... - Hey, Shiv? Fuck off.
那 我还是去客房睡觉吧
So, I'm probably just gonna sleep in the guest room
这样免得吵醒你
so I don't keep you awake.
呃 你在开玩笑吗
Uh, are you kidding me?
怎么了 这样我们都能睡得更好
What? We'll both sleep better.
汤姆
Tom.
拜托
Come on.
我们只是...我们俩已经...
We've just... We've gotten...
搅进去了 好吗
tangled up, okay?
亲爱的
Honey,
你是我唯一可以谈论这件事的人
you're the only one I can talk to about this stuff.
我需要你
I need you.
-现在 我要作出一个...  -嗯嗯
- Now, I have a choice... - Mm-hmm.
...决定 要么选吉尔
... to make. It's either Gil,
要么选爸爸
or it's Dad.
这有点让人抓狂
And it's a bit of a headfuck.
好的
Okay.
那 我们慢慢分析一下
Well, let's break it down.
因为我一直是这么想的
'Cause here's what I've been thinking.
-嗯嗯  -如果是一个好人...
- Mm-hmm. - What if a good person...
在掌管韦斯达呢
ran Waystar?
是的 我知道  韦斯达 这...
Yeah, I know. Waystar, it's...
你知道的 这是家族企业
You know, it's the family business.
是你继承的遗产
It's your inheritance.
但是 你知道 你看到过你父亲对肯德尔的所作所为
But, you know, you saw what your dad did to Kendall.
他对你做同样的事情 完全有可能
There's gotta be a chance he'll do the same to you.
一旦他掌控了你 就会对你感到厌烦
Get bored of you once he's got you.
我也不知道 也许你应该
I dunno. Maybe it's about
保留你的选择权 西沃恩
keeping your options open, Siobhan.
哦耶 是的
Oh, yeah. Yes.
你能不能...
Can you not just...
看看事态怎么发展 做多手准备
see how it goes and keep the plates spinning?
像迪克·莫里斯一样 在后面运筹帷幄[克林顿总统的竞选顾问]
Go Dick Morris, run things from out back?
是啊
Yeah.
嗯
Uh-huh.
这就是预案
That's the play.
好的 2号办公室在哪个地方
Okay, where are we on office two?
我想明天就开始运作
I wanna be operational by tomorrow.
他们现在在外面
They're outside right now.
我们走吧
Let's go.
-技术人员在路上了吗  -嗯嗯
- IT's on their way? - Mm-hmm.
他们知道去哪里吗 七楼 对吗
They know where it's going, seventh floor, right?
都准备好了吗
We all set?
三分钟
Three minutes.
好了 伙计们
Okay, guys.
各位 我想占用大家片刻
Everybody, if I could just have a second.
我只是想告诉大家一些最新的进展
I just wanted to update you on a couple of developments.
呃 有些人可能已经注意到了
Uh, some of you may have noticed
服务器已经关闭
servers are down.
我们将在七楼设立一个卫星办公室
And we're setting a satellite office on seven.
而且 恐怕我必须通知你们
And I'm afraid I have to inform you,
你们都被开除了
you are all dismissed.
是的 你们...你们都被解雇了
Yeah. You're... You're all fired.
所以 请你们将你们的笔记本电脑放在原地
So, if you can leave your laptops where they are,
交出你们的通行证
and hand in your passes,
安保人员现在会进来
security will be coming around now.
你们经历过的事情 我都经历过
I've been through everything you've shown me.
食品和大麻
Food and weed,
这是唯一的两个带来收入的垂直领域
those are the only two verticals
所以我们保留了这两项业务
driving revenue, so we're folding them in
现在 你们都可以离开了
and, uh, yeah, you're all free to leave.
开玩笑吧
This is a joke.
你们有15分钟的时间收拾个人财物
You have 15 minutes to gather your belongings
然后离开大楼
and exit the building.
离职协议将于近期交给大家
Separation agreements will be handed around shortly.
每满一年工作年限可以领到一周的遣散费
One week of severance per year served,
而且必须完全保密
with full non-disclosure.
对外发布小视频 只能领到三天的遣散费
Post your little videos. You get three days.
什么...
What the f...
未休完的假期将不予赔偿
Unused vacation days will not be reimbursed.
健康福利将在本月底
Health benefits will be terminated
终止
at the end of the month.
就这样
That's it.
我要感谢大家的辛勤工作
I'd like to thank you all for your hard work.
你个人渣
You piece of shit.
-你就这点能耐吗  -操你妈
- Is that all you got? - Fuck you.
操你妈 伙计
Fuck you, man!
喂 喂
Hey. Hey!
肯德尔 你他妈的在做什么
Kendall, what the fuck are you doing?
他妈的发生什么了
What the fuck is going on?
噢 抱歉 呃 斗篷和匕首[秘密行动]
Yeah, sorry about the, uh, cloak and dagger.
我只是需要点时间整理你的烂摊子
I just needed some time to untangle all your shit,
找到利润中心
find the profit centers,
让工会远离我们
keep the union off our back.
我们已经在七楼全面投入运营了
We're already fully operational on seven.
-为什么  -因为我爸让我这么干的
- Why? - Because my dad told me to.
因为你爸让你这么干的
Because your dad told you to?
天啦
Jesus Christ.
因为你爸让你这么干的
Because your dad told you to?
你...你把公司搞死了 兄弟
You... You fucked it, bro.
嗯
Uh-huh.
去祸害别的鸡窝吧 傻逼
Go find some other chicken coop, cunt.
什么...
What...
你他妈的是在开玩笑吗
Are you fucking kidding me?
因为你爸让你这么干的
Because your dad told you to!
你他妈是个白痴吗
Are you a fucking idiot?
肯德尔
Kendall!
哟 肯 哟 怎么样
Yo, Ken. Yo, how's it going?
挺好的 格雷格
All good, Greg.
只是 你知道的 在各种错误的地方寻找爱情
Just, you know, looking for love in all the wrong places.
是啊
Yeah.
不 伙计 确实
No, dude, exactly.
听着 肯 我 呃
Listen, Ken, I was, uh,
我超级疲惫... 我的腿痛得要死了
super wiped and I... My legs are just killing me.
还有我的腰背部
And my lower back.
所以 你看可不可以把你的派对挪到你的公寓去
So do you think you could maybe bring the party up to yours?
-到我的地方吗  -到你的地方
- Up to mine? - Up to your place.
噢 我觉得不行 格雷格
Yeah, I don't think so, Greg.
你知道吗 我现在 就像...
You know, I'm just, like...
我他妈就像数码界的盖茨比 正在找小妞寻欢
I'm looking for pussy like a fuckin' techno Gatsby.
绝对是 那是...
Hell yeah! That's...
是的 伙计 嗯...
Hell yeah, man. Um...
还有...某个你认识的人可能正在
There's also... some of your acquaintances are maybe
我的卧室里乱搞
humping in my bedroom?
你能不能...或者...
If you c... Or...
跟他们说说...
Can talk to them...
明天某个时候
I might like to go for a run
我可能想去跑个步 如果我们能腾出时间的话
sometime tomorrow, if we can make a space.
我需要测试一下我的腿筋...
I need to test the hamstrings...
但是不能有偷拍
But no paps.
我不需要再拍一张让我看上去像个软耷耷的鸡巴的照片
I don't need another shot of me looking like a used dick.
你是那个人 对吧 你就是那个人
You're him, right? You're the guy.
他们是这么说的
So they tell me.
很高兴认识你 伙计 我喜欢你 伙计
Good to meet you, man! I like you, man.
没有像您这样的人 我什么都不是
I'm nothing without people like you.
嘿
Hey,
你和我 等选举结束了
you and me, when this work gets done,
我们去喝啤酒 你觉得怎么样
we go get a beer. What do you say?
-好的  -好吗
- Yeah! - Okay?
-好的 不错  -好啊
- Yeah. Cool. - All right.
-很高兴见到你 不错  -嗯 不错
- Great to meet you. All right. - Yeah, yeah.
嘿 你想来点凝胶吗
Hey, you want some gel?
什么
Sorry?
普瑞来 洗手用的
Some Purell, for your hand.
你有多久没接触过无产阶级了
How long's it been since you touched a prole?
我"谢谢"你了 小西
No thank you, Shiv.
哦 说嘛 我... 我在开玩笑
Oh, come on. I'm... I'm kidding.
这到底是什么笑话呢
The joke being what, exactly?
我在街上遇到一个人之后
That I wanna sanitize my hand
我就想给我的手消毒吗
after I meet with a guy in the street?
谢谢了 但是不用洗手 我很好
Thank you. No. I'm good.
没错 这个笑话很烂 小西
Yeah, it's a pretty shitty joke, Shiv.
我只是说
I'm just saying
我认为 也许我们需要
that I think that maybe we need to be
对工人阶级有更多的尊重
more respectful of the working folk.
即使在我们内部也一样
Even internally?
-我的意思是...  -好的 是的 我明白了 吉尔
- I mean... - Okay, yeah. I get it Gil.
我不希望我们掉进那个陷阱
I don't want us to fall into that trap.
不 对...对不起 小西
No, I... I'm sorry, Shiv,
但是我只是觉得 可能你喜欢所谓的阳春白雪
but I just think that maybe you like in a kind of a bubble
这种笑话对你的家人和朋友来说
and this kind of joke is okay around your family
还可以
and friends.
别他妈跟我来这套
Don't fucking give me that.
你说什么
Excuse me?
不要因为你出卖了自己的灵魂而让我内疚
Don't pull a guilt trip on me 'cause you're selling your soul.
对不起 我们之间有什么问题吗
I'm sorry, do we have a problem here?
天啦 小西 你需要吃点东西休息会吗
Jesus, Shiv, you need a banana and a nap?
我想 也许我们私下再继续这个对话
I think maybe we continue this conversation in private.
为什么
Why?
你不想让他知道
You don't want him to know
你嘴里还含着我老爸的鸡鸡吗
you've still got my dad's cock in your mouth?
我正在讨论你推荐的一个安排
I was discussing an arrangement you recommended.
哦 是啊 你是 你刚刚难道不是...
Oh, yeah, you did. Didn't you just, y...
当然讨论过
Certainly discussed it.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你带我去达成一项交易 你告诉我应该接受
You're riding me over a deal you told me to take.
不过你很快就接受了 不是吗
Took it pretty quick though, didn't you?
立场改变得真他妈快
Rolled over really fucking fast.
而现在你来者不拒...
And now you're taking reach-arounds and...
坐波音787专机
flights on a 787.
这话从何说起 西沃恩
Where's this coming from, Siobhan?
对不起 我想也许我们应该...
I'm sorry, I think maybe we should just...
重新评估
reassess.
也许我...竞选顾问的角色 在后台运作
Perhaps I... Dick Morris things, operate from the background?
嗯 好的 是啊
Uh-huh. Okay. Yeah.
不 你知道我怎么想的吗 我觉得你说对了
No, you know what I think? I think you're right.
我认为我们需要更全面地重新评估
I think we need to reassess more comprehensively.
我认为内特是对的 你...
I think Nate is right, that your...
和汤姆 和泛美网络科技的关系...
connections to Tom, ATN, are...
让你分心了
a distraction.
是吗 你知道吗 实际上 我不干了
Oh yeah? Well you know what? Actually, I'm out.
实际上 我刚刚把你解雇了 小西
Actually, I just fired you, Shiv.
如果你注意到了的话
If you'd even noticed.
好吧 我他妈先不干的 你要是耳朵有在听的话
Well, I already fuckin' quit, if you had any antennae.
好了 搞定了
Okay, it's done.
沃尔特废了
Vaulter's dead.
工资单上有四百七十六个
Four-hundred and seventy-six off the payroll,
全职员工 自由记者...
full-timers, freelance...
我 呃 谈妥了提前解除合同的协议
I, uh, negotiated an early break from the lease
然后聘请了一名编辑和五名实习生
and hired an editor and five interns
维持剩下两个垂直领域的运营
for the two remaining verticals,
其余的将由用户生成
the rest will be user-generated,
评论 上传图片 所有这些东西
reviews, upload pics, all that stuff.
此外 我在沃尔特的工作人员离开之前
Also, I harvested a ton of ideas
收获了大量的点子
from the Vaulter staff before they left.
知识产权和初创企业的想法
IP and start-up ideas.
大多数是 你懂的 废话 但是...说不定有什么好点子
Most of it's, you know, bullshit but... you never know.
我们会宣称 你试图让沃尔特保持活力
We'll say you tried to keep it alive.
勇敢的努力 等等
Valiant efforts, et cetera.
我没事 我会接受的
I'm good. I'll wear it.
我得接这个电话
I should take this.
-怎么了  -爸
- Yeah? - Dad?
我跟吉尔辞职了
I told Gil.
我准备好了 我们开始吧
I'm ready. Let's get started.
开始... 让我进入公司
Start... looping me in.
这很棒
That's great.
我再联系你
I'll be in touch.
一切都好吗
Everything okay?
没事 就是平常的头痛
Oh, yeah. Usual headaches.
嘿 我应该参加这个吗
Hey. Should I be in this?
罗曼
Roman,
从现在开始 你哥哥将在这里工作
your brother's gonna be working in here from now on.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
我需要他参与代理权争夺战
I need him across the proxy battle.
我们承受不起沟通失误的后果
Can't afford communication slips.
好吗
Okay?
你还在等什么
What are you waiting for?
等我亲你吗
A kiss?
滚出去吧 走了 再见
Fuck off. Be gone. Bye bye.
怎么了 我可以"帮"你吗
Yes? Can I help you?
你他妈的看个毛啊
Fuck you looking at?
你做得很好 儿子
You did good, son.
谢谢
Thank you.
请自便
Make yourself at home.
还舒适吧
Comfortable?
嘿  可以给我一包黄色的美国精神吗[香烟]
Hey. Can I get a pack of American Spirit Yellow?
还要个火机
One of these.
ZIMUXIA.CN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
有些人对此有疑虑...
There were some doubts as to...
我们现在真正需要的是不是一次收购
whether an acquisition is really what we need right now.
正是  越大的收购越好
It is. The bigger the better.
我志在必得
And I have it.
这是一场灾难
This is a disaster.
我们需要阻止他
We need to stop him.
今年的公司会议 你能袖手旁观吗
Could you sit out the corporate retreat this year?
不 我去才能加油鼓劲
Nah. It's a morale-booster.
有人阻挠这次收购
Someone spiked the deal.
是你们中间哪个小子干的
Which one of you boys did it?
宣布一下 我 必 胜
Here's news: I... will... win.